- [Narrator] Hello, and welcome to Big Data University.
In this course, you will get answers
to fundamental questions such as what is Big Data?
Where is Big Data coming from?
And, how can businesses derive value from it?
The syllabus goes beyond the hype of Big Data
to talk about adoption, and the skills required
for data scientists in the Big Data era.
We will cover the Vs that have come to define Big Data,
velocity, volume, variety, and veracity,
as well as the final, and perhaps most important V, value.
We will look for some use cases for Big Data, and cover
important considerations, like governance and security.
We will also provide a high-level introduction to Hadoop.
We discuss what it is, and why
it is relevant to a Big Data discussion.
Once you have taken this course,
you will be familiar with the terminology used
in Big Data conversations, and you will have an idea
of how Big Data can be applied in different industries.
Thank you for taking the time to learn more about Big Data.
Happy learning.